nfshost.com 2007-07-20

# NearlyFreeSpeech.NET Privacy Policy

## NearlyFreeSpeech.Net Privacy Policy

NearlyFreeSpeech.NET's Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you use our services. This policy does not apply to entities that we do not control, including member sites hosted by our service.

We collect personally identifiable information when you register for service with us. We also automatically receive and record information from our systems about your use of our services. We use this information to fulfill your requests related to our services.

We will not sell, trade or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. Ever. Period. We will not disclose your personally identifiable information to any third party without your prior consent unless legally compelled to do so. We will attempt to notify you any time we are forced to disclose your personally identifiable information unless we are legally prevented from doing so.

We will cooperate with all investigations conducted by law enforcement authorities of the United States of America when legally required to do so. Cooperation with law enforcement authorities from other countries and cooperation when it is not legally required are at our sole discretion. Our discretion looks favorably on freedom and justice, and unfavorably on oppression and violence. Unless legally prohibited, we will inform you of any cooperation we provide to any law enforcement authorities.

We use session cookies on our site. These cookies should not be permanently stored on your computer; restarting your browser should eliminate them. We use these cookies **only** for the following purposes: 

  1. To manage your login information in our member interface. (required)
  2. To allow you to personalize your use of our forums. (optional)
  3. In conjunction with our master installation of phpMyAdmin. (required only if you use our phpMyAdmin)

You may be connecting through an intermediary such as AOL that adds tracking cookies for their own purposes. We recommend using our secure site to defeat such illicit monitoring.

We will not use your personally identifiable information to market our products and services to you unless you specifically indicate you wish us to do so. We will not use your personally identifiable information to market third party products and services to you.

If for any reason you terminate your service, we will destroy active records containing your personally identifiable information as soon as it is reasonable to do so. Some information may continue to exist in our archived records. If we terminate your service, we may retain enough information to prevent you from signing up for service in the future.
